

Senior Full-Stack Developer with 12 years of experience in building and maintaining web applications. Dedicated to delivering quality, efficient solutions to challenging problems, willing to take ownership of core components. Team player, continuous learner, open source contributor.

**Technologies** 

Ruby (Ruby on Rails, dry-rb), Javascript/ES6 (React, jQuery), Elixir, Elasticsearch, Redis, PostgreSQL, MySQL, AWS, Heroku, Serverless.

Experience

## Sellektor

Mar 2017 - present

CTO, partner

Architected and built **Sellektor.com**, an aggregation platform for e-commerce products, with its main components: search engine driven by distributed data integration pipeline (processing millions of products from ~100 data sources every day) and custom ranking algorithms, image processing service, tracking and analytics services.

Humante 2016 - 2017

Founder, Tech Lead

Led a team of 6 developers building web and mobile applications for Europeand US-based start-ups.

Worked on company's own product - predictive recommendations service aimed at e-commerce industry.

## Kazimierz Wielki University, Bydgoszcz, Poland

2016 - 2017

Group Mentor

Mentored a group of students during their IT course and team project.

Monterail 2009 - 2016

Co-founder, Tech Lead, Team Manager

Recruited, coached and managed a team of 10+ developers working on projects for international clients. Involved in software architecture and design, development, project management, business development and creating company's internal processes.

Netguru 2007 - 2009

Software Engineer

Developed web applications with Ruby, PHP and Javascript.

Education

Adam Mickiewicz University, Poznań, Poland

2003 - 2009

Computer Science